I've worked with hundreds of online
businesses,
and the majority of them share the
exact same reason as to why they don't
grow, as to why they struggle to get
clients,
and why they struggle to grow their sales
year on year, let alone month on
month. And to summarize it best,
it's because they are content pussies.
And in this video,
I'm going to explain why.
And if you get your feelings hurt easily,
maybe skip this video and watch someone
else's. Now, content pussies, for a start,
share lots of the same
traits. And one of the first
is they have this inclination in the back
of their
head that they just need to nail paid ads.
They think that if they get their paid ads
working, they can just pay their way to
get in front of people.
But there's a problem with this.
For your paid ads to do incredibly well,
your organic content has to do well.
Think about your organic content being the
cake and your paid ads being the icing.
People think that they can just get really
good at making icing, and that will
cover the fact that there's a shit cake
underneath.
Because all you're doing with paid ads
is you're boosting posts.
But if those posts don't connect with
humans,
it doesn't matter how much money you
put behind them.
And a lot of people out there know
that you're a content pussy,
so they'll say thing in their own ads to
make you feel that that's the way out.
The reason your business isn't growing
is because you've not nailed paid ads.
I'm afraid that's bollocks.
If you want to win with paid ads,
you have to win
organic first. And to get good at organic,
you need a lot of repetitions, a lot of
eating shit, a lot of failed attempts,
and you've got to learn not only what
you're
good at, but what the audience wants.
For instance, an example of
that would be anyone new to creating
YouTube is
probably being a content pussy.
That's why they've not started YouTube.
And they go, "Oh,
I don't know what to do." I'm like, "Well,
you make 10 videos
about 10 different topics." What topics?
I don't care.
Because then once you've done those 10
videos and done those 10 topics, one video
will have done better than everything
else.
An example within that example,
friend of mine has a cookbook, hundreds of
thousands of followers,
hasn't started on YouTube.
I said,
"Why not just teach people 10 different
things to cook?" Then one of those
videos might surprise you. You go, "Oh,
I always thought this recipe was going to
do well,
but the hot cross buns video seemed to do
almost twice as well.
Go away and now make more hot cross buns
videos." If the trend continues, there's
obviously an interest. If it doesn't,
it was just a fluke.
What if that keeps happening? Well,
then why not create a hot cross bun lead
magnet? Then once you've created that,
they can download something in exchange
for
their email.
Then you could upsell them into a hot
cross bun cookery course, or
they might buy your apron, your hat,
your cookbook, whatever it is, that you
wouldn't have known about the hot cross
bun desire without some kind of
diversity across your portfolio of content
as to what people are into.
But by being a pussy,
you're never going to be able to get those
signals back from
your audience. Then in enough time,
who knows?
You could run some paid promotion behind
the hot cross bun recipe
kit or whatever it is.
You know what I mean?
I don't even like hot cross buns.
But if you're too much of a content pussy,
you're not going to get that feedback
from your audience.
You're not going to be able to build the
very thing that they
want.
So you haven't earned the right to
dominate well with paid ads
because you haven't even learned how to
dominate with organic.
So your next question
is probably going to be,
"So how do I get attention with
organic content as a content pussy?" Well,
the good news is, if you don't get
attention, no one sees.
And what I mean by that
is everyone has this crippling
fear that if they make a mistake,
it's the worst thing ever.
Let me tell you, there
are plenty of ways where making a mistake
is bad.
If you jizz in the wrong woman,
you now have a child with someone forever.
The cost of making a mistake there, dire.
If you share your crypto wallet key
and someone takes your life savings,
that mistake is dire.
If you punch someone in a street fight,
they hit their head on the concrete
and they die and you go to jail, that is a
mistake that is really bad. But
if you make a piece of content that
bombs, no one sees it,
quite literally because it bombed.
So when you weigh up what failure looks
like in some areas of your life to the
other, you're like, "Oh,
there's actually not really anything
that scary by
making mistakes." If anything, there
are benefits to making those mistakes
because those mistakes show you what works
and what didn't.
You get feedback from that.
You don't get feedback from actual bad
mistakes in
life apart from you're going to jail
or you're back to
£0 or dollars.
So you get to put out this grand
landscape of different varied content,
which should all be about people's
problems,
by the way. No one cares about you.
No one cares about your clients.
All they care about is themselves.
Now,
sometimes you can portray your own stories
or your clients'
stories to get the person watching to give
a shit, but ultimately, they only care
about themselves. So
if you want to get someone's attention,
make a reel that
really helps them solve a certain problem.
And you go, "Oh,
where do I get the idea of problems from?"
Most of you should be
working with people. Quite literally,
the questions that they ask you are gold
dust.
I'm actually about to hire someone who
does a certain job,
and all I want them to do
is feed me the questions
that their clients are asking
them,
and I'm going to pay them for it because
I've lost touch in personal training
a bit with the actual problems
that people are facing in 2026.
So I said,
"If you tell me what your clients want to
know, the issues, the
insecurities, the fears,
all of those things,
I'll pay you for it because I need
that to help me to make better content."
So if you're a content pussy, you're
probably wondering,
how often should you post?
As often as fucking possible.
A friend of mine, as an example,
has posted hundreds of recipes only to
Instagram. So not to Facebook,
not to TikTok, not to YouTube Shorts.
And she's got loads of spare time. I
was like,
"Why haven't you taken all those old
posts and reposted them?" And I go,
"Why should you do that?
Repost them to Instagram as well.
If posting them once got you 200,000
followers,
imagine what posting them two
or three times would get you." Then she
could put out one new post a day plus two
old posts.
That's three posts a day. Now,
I would never in history ever said
that you
need to post more than once a day.
But actually, times are changing
and I'm hiring
someone else to help me put out more
posts. How many?
15 a day. Yep.
I'm gonna hire someone full-time to help
me put out 15
reels a day. Probably 15 trial reels,
of which four will get posted,
the ones that
do the best. How often? Every day.
So those of you out there posting three
times
a week. Oh, that's cute.
I'm gonna do five times that in a fucking
day.
So if you want to play in the big boy
leagues and have nice things that big
boys have like [car revving] you're gonna
have to step it up a
bit. One a day minimum.
Doesn't have to be a beautifully curated
reel.
It just has to be a piece of content.
Now,
as your business mentor,
I can accept your reels bombing.
If I turn up to your Instagram
and it's just bomb after bomb after bomb,
fine.
If I turn up to your Insta
and you haven't posted,
you've been inactive, that I
cannot tolerate.
Because most stand-up comedians
that have amazing sets have eaten
shit so many times. They've tried jokes.
They've done works in progress.
They've gone out with their notepads.
So if comedians have to go out
and eat shit and bomb,
why do you think you get to
go all the way to the top in this content
creation game without fucking eating a
bit of shit? Now,
you're probably crippled as a content
pussy by a fear of
judgment. So let's get into it. You
are not worried about what your clients
think.
You're worried about what other people in
your industry think.
As an accountant talking about corp tax,
you're wondering what other accountants
will think. As a chef putting out recipes,
you're worried what other chefs will
think. As a personal trainer, as a coach,
you're worried about what other coaches
will think. They are the only people
that will never buy your shit.
That's like being a fucking butcher's
and worrying what the vegans are thinking.
Do you understand how moronic it
is to be feared to be judged by peers,
literally the only people
that will never buy your shit?
And if you want to get over the fear of
anything, action is a fucking amazing way
to do it. So what I mean by that, in CBT,
cognitive behavioral therapy, I'm
pretty sure there's something called
exposure therapy.
So if you're scared of something,
you should expose yourself to it.
Now, if you're scared of spiders,
don't go jump in a pit full of a million
fucking huntsman spiders. Not that.
But you could find a really small,
non-scary spider and hold it in your hand
for a
minute. And guess what?
It would help you be less scared of
spiders.
If you hate public speaking,
you could do some public speaking to a
crowd of 10
people, do some volunteer work,
whatever it is.
If you're afraid of asking out girls for
their number, you could start
complimenting females when you're out
and about and just saying, "Hey,
I like your
shoes." There are ways
that you can break down the fears of
anything you have by
just getting more exposure to it.
So you'll never guess what's fucking
rocket
science.
If you're scared of posting content,
where do you think the remedy is to
getting better at that?
Posting more content.
Now, it doesn't have to be a camera,
it doesn't have to be a public place.
It could be anywhere.
I grew to a million followers posting,
sitting on my bedroom
floor with a tripod and a camera.
The only way to get over fear of judgment
is to
put out fucking loads of content. And
if you think there's any way around that,
you're a fucking cretin.
And as a content pussy,
you're probably thinking, "Oh, is
social media really worth it?
Oh." Business, for years,
has been on hard mode.
It's been so fucking difficult.
Then social media came along.
Think about this.
Personal training's been around for
decades.
Then Facebook came along, and I was like,
"Hold on.
I can just put videos out on Facebook
and people come to me
wanting personal training?
Are you fucking kidding me?
So I've no longer got to walk the floor.
I could just put out videos
and people will come to me." I was like,
"Wow,
this is the best fucking thing ever." Now,
I can put this video out and
people will click in the link in
description, buy my YouTube course,
join my
mentorship.
I don't have to do sales calls
or DM strangers.
I can just have conversations with people
when I'm in my car and make money.
Are you kidding me? And the money
that I get paid from these videos allows
my
family to live in a beautiful home,
for my missus to drive a luxury car, for
us to fly business class
when we go to Tokyo in a few weeks.
And social media is free.
I don't pay YouTube. Oh,
I do have YouTube Premium.
I don't know how people live without
YouTube Premium.
But I don't pay to post there.
Billboard's expensive.
Advert's expensive.
Every single means of marketing is
expensive. Social media is free.
Is social media actually worth it?
Yeah.
It's the fucking lowest hanging fruit,
the easiest thing that you could ever
possibly do to win over new business.
Better yet,
you get to spend so long in front of
people chatting to them that they
get to know you. Most of you,
if you go see me in the street,
if you go stop me
when I'm having a coffee and say hello,
you're like a friend I've not met yet, and
I think that's wonderful.
I think that's great.
And so many of you out there
are just a few thousand videos,
and I know a few
thousand seems scary,
but let's rewind a bit.
If I said you put out 1,000 videos,
you don't check how much things cost at
dinner,
you get to pay off your parents' mortgage
or retire them early, and your
future family never have to worry about a
thing. Would you do it? Probably.
So what's the question?
What's the problem? What's the hesitation?
Because if you do it right,
it's been proven over
and over in front of you, Sean
Casey, Adam Sullivan, myself.
I can't think of a time
that someone's put out
thousands of bits of content
and not completely changed their life.
Now,
what's a realistic timeframe for growth?
Some of you will do it in 500 posts.
Let's say short form.
The majority, 1,000.
I reckon you have to put out 150 YouTube
videos, and
I reckon you have to grow your email list
to a good 5,000 before people start
buying. Now, when it comes to timeframes,
here's the thing.
For some people, that's five years.
For some people, it's three months.
But the main determining differentiating
factor here isn't how long it is, it's how
much you work in that period of time.
It's like weight loss, right?
If you want to lose 10 kilograms,
you can do that in three weeks if you went
fucking hard.
But the realistic thing you want to do
is probably do it over two,
three months.
But then some people drag their heels
and spend a fucking year losing
10 kilograms. This
is the biggest hindrance to people
becoming
successful,
and it's the fact they're fucking pussies
when it comes to content.
They're not willing to just pump,
to have videos bomb, to test.
You understand some of the people you're
competing with in your industry are
putting up hundreds of adverts to find one
that does well, 300
advert creatives to find one
that does well, and you're there thinking,
"Oh, I
tried that reel.
It didn't work." Do it again. Post more.
Go to twice a day.
Because either your diary is full of
clients that pay you really good money,
or if you're broken skin, you've got
so much time throughout the day
that you should be posting more than me.
Every single waking hour
is an opportunity for you to post more,
and you use it to
fuck around and play around with your dick
in your hand.
And it's not even
that you're wasting your time
or wasting your opportunity.
It's the fact that as you do that,
other people are doing what you won't,
and they are going to win the clients
that you didn't.
They're going to get the recognition
that you won't.
They're going to sit in parts of the plane
that you can't.
And it's not even
that you're not in business class.
It's going to be this urge
that you have in the back of your mind
knowing if you
had just committed for those few years,
you could've got so much more done.
I'll tell you something I didn't intend to
tell you in this video.
2021, a lot of my friends got rich,
really rich.
It was only when I went to their houses
that I realized, fuck.
Whilst I was playing Call of Duty
and having the best years of my life,
other
people did so well
that their kids will never have to work,
which I don't think is
a good thing,
but it's nice to have as an option.
And these massive houses, beautiful cars.
And it's not that I'm jealous of their
success, it's that I'm annoyed
that I didn't
use that time right.
And I've got friends now at the moment
being content pussies,
and I say to them,
"Ignore everything you feel today.
Just ask yourself this.
If things get harder,
which very likely they could,
will you be able to forgive
yourself for not going all in now?"
Because there's a part of me
that eats away at
myself for the opportunities
that I missed four or five years ago,
and I'm making
up for it now. Got a chip on my shoulder,
for sure.
But if you do not maximize the next two,
three years, if I don't do it, I'm not
going to be able to forgive myself.
When I started, it was just Facebook.
There was no Instagram. YouTube was there,
but not quite the same platform.
People had to follow you to see your
posts. Now, there's so much opportunity.
Cameras that you can put in your car,
wireless mics that make you sound good,
algorithms that show people content,
your content,
when they don't even follow you.
To be a content pussy in 2026,
it's just one of the worst decisions,
because it
is a decision. You have two parts in life,
action, inaction.
You either did it or you didn't.
The girl that you didn't ask out,
you didn't ask.
It wasn't fate, it was you.
Your life right now
is a series of decisions of things
you've done and things you haven't.
And even if you never buy my programs,
never join my courses, never join my
mentorship, whatever,
which most of you won't, and that's fine,
if there's one
skill that you really need to develop for
the future, it's to not
be a content pussy. Everything
that I've managed to do in the last few
years,
books, events, cars, houses, fiancée,
child, social media
content opened everything.
And just don't sleep on
that opportunity because I
honestly don't know
if you'll be able to forgive yourself in a
few years' time.
You're scared, I get it. So was everyone.
But some of us just decided to get on with
it anyway. I think George St.
Pierre said, "Courage is not
that you're not scared.
It's that you are scared
and you do it anyway." Links in the
description.
Use them, don't use them.
You can lead a horse to water,
but you can't make it
drink. Hope you enjoyed that video.
If you're not going to buy my shit,
[clicks tongue] click
that video there because
YouTube says you need it.